missingkids.org 2004-06-10

# Privacy Policy

National Center for Missing & Exploited Children  
Web Site Privacy Policy 

The National Center for Missing & Exploited Children® (NCMEC) respects your privacy and your concerns about maintaining it. This privacy policy is intended to help you understand our online information security practices.

**Information We Collect**

You have several opportunities to submit your personally identifiable information on this web site. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, address, E-mail address, telephone number, and the like.

For instance, you may wish to receive brochures from us, or be added to an E-mail list so that you can receive important information about missing or exploited children. In those cases, we collect personal information necessary to fulfill your request.

Or you may have information about a missing or exploited child and wish to submit that information over our web site, such as through our CyberTipline®. In such cases we ask for your personal information.

You may also wish to make a donation to NCMEC over our web site, in which case we collect your personal information, including credit-card information.

**Information That We Share With Third Parties**

In cases where a visitor to our web site makes a report about a missing or exploited child and, in doing so, submits personally identifiable information, we forward such information to appropriate law-enforcement agencies for investigation.

When you submit credit-card information to us, we immediately forward that information to a service that charges your account. We do not save or store your credit card number, although we do retain your name and address and may use that information to communicate with you in the future.

From time to time, we supply to third-party vendors personal information about visitors who wish to receive information from us. Such vendors may include, for example, organizations that process mailings for us. Those vendors have entered non-disclosure agreements with us so that personal information is used only to respond to the visitors' requests and is not shared with any other entity or individual.

Occasionally we will share aggregate information about our visitors with certain third parties. "Aggregate information" shows visitor activity as a whole but does not identify any individual user. For example, we may post a survey to which visitors can elect to respond. We might share the results of that survey with interested third parties, or we may use the information to improve our services and/or our web site.

Except as described in this section, we will not sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose your personal information to any party for any reason.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data that is deposited on your hard drive by some web sites. When you return to that site the cookie will tell the site that you have been there before. The site can then offer you products or ads that are tailored to your interests. We do not use cookies to track your use of our site, although we employ cookies to make your search of our missing children posters more efficient.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our web site contains links to other web sites. This privacy policy does not apply to those Web sites, nor do the privacy policies of those web sites apply to us. We urge you to review the privacy policies of any web site you may access through our site.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

NCMEC may change this privacy policy from time to time. We will notify you of any such changes by posting notice of the changes on our start-up screen. If you use NCMEC's site following notice of any changes, your use will indicate that you acknowledge such changes and agree to be bound by them.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 30, 2003.
